sportsinjuryclinic.net 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy & Cookies - Sportsinjuryclinic.net

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

VIRTUAL SPORTS INJURY CLINIC LIMITED PRIVACY POLICY

Virtual Sports Injury Clinic Limited (“We”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our [terms of use](https://www.sportsinjuryclinic.net/about-us/terms-conditions) and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is Virtual Sports Injury Clinic Limited of 2 Back Lane, Wymondham, Norfolk, NR18 0QB.

### Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.sportsinjuryclinic.net (our site). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

### IP addresses

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system, and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

### Cookies

A Cookie file is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser while a user is browsing a website. This web site uses cookies to anonymously track site visitors through Google Analytics. We do not store or use our own web site specific cookies.

If you would like to know more about our use of cookies please [contact us](https://www.sportsinjuryclinic.net/about-us/contact-us).

When the user browses the same website in the future, the data stored in the cookie can be retrieved by the website to notify the website of the user’s previous activity. Cookies were designed to be a reliable mechanism for websites to remember the state of the website or activity the user had taken in the past. This can include clicking particular buttons, logging in, or a record of which pages were visited by the user even months or years ago. More information on that topic can be found on Wikipedia.

Purposes of storage and gaining access to cookies:

  * Website personalisation (for example: saving font size, sight challenged version of website or template version)
  * Saving data or user’s decisions (for example no need to enter login and password on every website, remembering login during the next visit, keeping information on products added to cart)
  * Social websites integration (for example: displaying your friends, fans or post publishing on Facebook or Google+ directly from the website)
  * Adjusting adverts that are displayed on the website
  * Creating website’s statistics and flow statistics between different websites

Below one can find links to sources showing how to set the conditions of storage and gaining access to cookies already stored in the user’s device for the most popular internet browsers.

  * Firefox
  * Chrome
  * Internet Explorer
  * Opera
  * Safari

Due to a vast number of technological solutions, it is not possible to publish clear guidelines on how to set the conditions of storage and gaining access to cookies using settings of all available devices and software installed on them. However, in most cases, select “Tools” or “Settings” and there find the section that corresponds to the configuration settings for cookies or for the management of privacy. Detailed information is usually provided by the manufacturer of the device or browser in a manual or on their website

### Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

### Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service when you choose to do so.
  * To notify you about changes to our service.

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers’ wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

### Disclosure of your information

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company, and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If Virtual Sports Injury Clinic Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our[ terms of use](https://www.sportsinjuryclinic.net/about-us/terms-conditions) and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Virtual Sports Injury Clinic Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by [contacting us](https://www.sportsinjuryclinic.net/about-us/contact-us).

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

### Access to information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

### Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.

### Contact

You are welcome to [contact us](https://www.sportsinjuryclinic.net/about-us/contact-us) with questions, comments, and requests regarding this privacy policy.
